<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SAİ</string>

    <string name="select_country">Select Country</string>
    <string name="select_energy_type">Select Energy Type</string>
    <string name="enter_usage">Enter Usage</string>
    <string name="calculate">Calculate</string>
    <string name="result_text">Your carbon footprint: %.2f kg CO2</string>



    <string name="first_fragment_label" translatable="false">İlk Fragment Başlığı</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label" translatable="false">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next" translatable="false">Next</string>
    <string name="previous" translatable="false">Previous</string>

    <string-array name="electric_types">
        <item>Solar</item>
        <item>Coal</item>
        <item>Barrage</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Heating_types">
        <item>Electric</item>
        <item>Coal</item>
        <item>Natural Gas</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Vehicle_types">
        <item>Disel</item>
        <item>LPG</item>
        <item>Gasolina</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Foods">
        <item>Red</item>
        <item>Chicken</item>
        <item>Milk</item>
        <item>Fruits</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="Main_title" translatable="false">What Is a Carbon Footprint?</string>
    <string name="short_answer_title" translatable="false">The short answer:</string>
    <string name="short_answer" translatable="false"> A “carbon footprint” is shorthand for all of a person or organization’s greenhouse
        gas emissions that contribute to climate change.</string>
    <string name="long_answer_title" translatable="false">A carbon footprint is a measure of the total amount of greenhouse gases,
        primarily carbon dioxide, that are emitted directly or indirectly by human activities. Understanding the carbon footprint is
        crucial as it helps to assess the impact of individual or organizational actions on climate change. The importance of reducing
        one\'s carbon footprint lies in mitigating global warming and its associated effects, such as extreme weather events,
        sea level rise, and loss of biodiversity. Various factors contribute to a carbon footprint, including energy consumption,
        transportation choices, diet, and waste generation. For instance, using fossil fuels for electricity, heating, and transportation
        significantly increases carbon emissions. Similarly, high meat consumption and food waste are major contributors to a larger carbon
        footprint. By adopting sustainable practices such as using renewable energy, opting for public transport or carpooling, and reducing
        meat intake, individuals and organizations can effectively lower their carbon footprint and contribute to a healthier planet.
    <string name="calculation">Calculation</string>"

</string>
    <string name="settings" translatable="false">Settings</string>
    <string name="what_footprint" translatable="false">what Footprint</string>
    <string name="calculation" translatable="false">Calculation</string>
    <string name="history" translatable="false">History</string>

    <string name="electric_carbon_footprint" translatable="false">ELECTRIC CARBON FOOTPRINT</string>
    <string name="warming_carbon_footprint" translatable="false">WARMING CARBON FOOTPRINT</string>
    <string name="fuel_carbon_footprint" translatable="false">FUEL CARBON FOOTPRINT</string>
    <string name="travel_carbon_footprint" translatable="false">TRAVEL CARBON FOOTPRINT</string>
    <string name="eat_carbon_footprint" translatable="false">EAT CARBON FOOTPRINT</string>
    <string name="your_total_carbon_footprint" translatable="false">YOUR TOTAL CARBON FOOTPRINT</string>
    <string name="beginningWarning" > Your countrys emission values will be used in the calculation.You can change this setting from the settings section.</string>

    <string name="electricty_warning" translatable="false">Warning! Your electricity usage results in high levels of CO2 emissions</string>
    <string name="heating_warning" translatable="false">Warning! Your heating usage results in high levels of CO2 emissions</string>
    <string name="fuel_warning" translatable="false">Warning! Your fuel usage results in high levels of CO2 emissions</string>
    <string name="travel_warning" translatable="false">Warning! Your travel usage results in high levels of CO2 emissions</string>
    <string name="eat_warning" translatable="false">Warning! Your eat usage results in high levels of CO2 emissions</string>

    <string-array name="Electricwarning_array">
        <item>You can reduce your electricity consumption by using energy-efficient devices such as LED bulbs and energy-saving white goods.</item>
        <item>Turn off or unplug electronic devices that you are not using. Even in standby mode, devices consume energy.</item>
        <item>If possible, take advantage of renewable energy sources by installing solar panels.</item>

    </string-array>

</resources>